## **YEN HUNG LIN**

----

hello@yenhunglin.com yenhunglin.com

#### SKILLS

Taiwanese

Computer Programs	Shop Skills
Sketch	Band saw
Invision	Bridgeport mill
Zeplin	Drill press
	Laser cutter
-	Miter saw
After Effects	Painting
-	Sanding
Photoshop	Vacuum forming
Illustrator	
InDesign	
-	<b>Scripting Languages</b>
Keyshot	HTMI
	CSS
	JS
Languages	JS
Mandarin Chinese	

Other

**ID Sketching** 

Package model making

#### SELECTED RECOMMENDATIONS

# Heidi Bullock // Chief Marketing Officer at Tealium

I feel very fortunate to have worked with Jeff. He is incredibly talented and can take a high level marketing concept and breath life into it. Jeff is also a unique talent because he is outstanding at UX as well, so companies can have a cohesive feel across external marketing and product. Jeff is thoughtful and responds well to feedback. He is someone I would hire again!

# **Tim Kennedy** // Graphic design + Packaging Manager at Speck Products

When Jeff joined our team at HTC San Francisco he started out in a blazing glory, and continued to shine for the duration of his time with us at HTC. Jeff's deft design skills and capable know how brought much needed support to our design team. While Jeff is a talented fellow, he's open-minded and has a willingness to explore new areas of design. Jeff has a genuine nature about him and is a kind, well-spoken man of may talents. I'd look forward to working with him again in the future!

#### SELECTED EXPERIENCES

#### Engagio // San Mateo, CA

2018-Present, Visual, UI Designer

Working with PM, UX designers, engineers, and the marketing team to define the visual and the interactive elements of the user interface for our products; keeping our team's UI library organized and up-to-date; and brand design projects.

#### MOCACARE // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2017-2018, UI/UX, Visual Designer

Working with the industrial design team and the product design team to locate user needs and to explore various solutions. Projects included MOCACARE hardware, packaging, and app.

# HTC // SF, CA + Taipei, Taiwan

2014-2015, Visual, Package Designer

Working with the industrial and packaging team on packaging, animation, UI, and graphic design. Also accompanied designers to factories, met with vendors for study of new materials, and built a good work relationship with vendors.

#### San Francisco Art Institute // SF, CA

2014, Graphic Design Intern

In charge of weekly event poster designs, gallery show invitation designs, school publications, and school event photo documentation.

#### CCA Sputnik Design Studio // SF, CA

2013, Graphic Designer

In charge of Phase Forward: First Year Exhibition 2013, CCA 2013 Annual Fashion Show, Upstart: CCA Commencement Events 2013, CCA Fashion Design Promotion Fall 2013, and CCA President's Letter Fall 2013.

### **EDUCATION**

# California College of the Arts

2013, BFA in Graphic Design